{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957642223","data":{"timestamp":" 946957642223"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 11190fb5-c779-4548-907e-3cb757ed8211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_G-R-D"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957645725","data":{"timestamp":" 946957645725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 11190fb5-c779-4548-907e-3cb757ed8211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_M-R-D"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957649246","data":{"timestamp":" 946957649246"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 11190fb5-c779-4548-907e-3cb757ed8211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_S-F-R"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957652423","data":{"timestamp":" 946957652423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 11190fb5-c779-4548-907e-3cb757ed8211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-W-Z"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957655661","data":{"timestamp":" 946957655661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 11190fb5-c779-4548-907e-3cb757ed8211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_G-R-T"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957659148","data":{"timestamp":" 946957659148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 11190fb5-c779-4548-907e-3cb757ed8211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_Z-R-G"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957662572","data":{"timestamp":" 946957662572"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 11190fb5-c779-4548-907e-3cb757ed8211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_Z-H-R"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957665871","data":{"timestamp":" 946957665871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 11190fb5-c779-4548-907e-3cb757ed8211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_G-L-R"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957669425","data":{"timestamp":" 946957669425"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 11190fb5-c779-4548-907e-3cb757ed8211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-Y-E"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957672791","data":{"timestamp":" 946957672791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 11190fb5-c779-4548-907e-3cb757ed8211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_L-T-R"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957678571","data":{"timestamp":" 946957678568"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 11190fb5-c779-4548-907e-3cb757ed8211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_R_L-T-R"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957702288","data":{"timestamp":" 946957702288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" f7b211ab-ea52-45aa-a320-4967755cdfec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_S_Z_R"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957708954","data":{"timestamp":" 946957708954"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" f7b211ab-ea52-45aa-a320-4967755cdfec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_N_R_B"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957715624","data":{"timestamp":" 946957715624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" f7b211ab-ea52-45aa-a320-4967755cdfec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_S_U"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957722239","data":{"timestamp":" 946957722239"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" f7b211ab-ea52-45aa-a320-4967755cdfec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_V_W_R"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957728867","data":{"timestamp":" 946957728867"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" f7b211ab-ea52-45aa-a320-4967755cdfec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_O_H"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957735499","data":{"timestamp":" 946957735499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" f7b211ab-ea52-45aa-a320-4967755cdfec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_V_Y_R"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957742123","data":{"timestamp":" 946957742123"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" f7b211ab-ea52-45aa-a320-4967755cdfec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_W_N_R"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957748750","data":{"timestamp":" 946957748750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" f7b211ab-ea52-45aa-a320-4967755cdfec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_J_D"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957755399","data":{"timestamp":" 946957755399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" f7b211ab-ea52-45aa-a320-4967755cdfec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_J_W"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957762077","data":{"timestamp":" 946957762076"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" f7b211ab-ea52-45aa-a320-4967755cdfec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_D_E"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957774144","data":{"timestamp":" 946957774143"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" f7b211ab-ea52-45aa-a320-4967755cdfec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_R..R.all.10.rand.say.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_R_D_E"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957797335","data":{"timestamp":" 946957797335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957799897","data":{"timestamp":" 946957799896"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957801507","data":{"timestamp":" 946957801506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957807664","data":{"timestamp":" 946957807663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" START_B"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957809984","data":{"timestamp":" 946957809983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957811608","data":{"timestamp":" 946957811607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957814259","data":{"timestamp":" 946957814259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957815875","data":{"timestamp":" 946957815874"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957818119","data":{"timestamp":" 946957818118"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957819733","data":{"timestamp":" 946957819733"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957822575","data":{"timestamp":" 946957822575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957824174","data":{"timestamp":" 946957824173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957826747","data":{"timestamp":" 946957826746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957828344","data":{"timestamp":" 946957828343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957830364","data":{"timestamp":" 946957830363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957831973","data":{"timestamp":" 946957831972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957842137","data":{"timestamp":" 946957842136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957843758","data":{"timestamp":" 946957843758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957846363","data":{"timestamp":" 946957846363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957847973","data":{"timestamp":" 946957847972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957850736","data":{"timestamp":" 946957850736"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957852337","data":{"timestamp":" 946957852337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957854834","data":{"timestamp":" 946957854833"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957856432","data":{"timestamp":" 946957856431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957859313","data":{"timestamp":" 946957859313"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957860906","data":{"timestamp":" 946957860905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957863507","data":{"timestamp":" 946957863507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957865088","data":{"timestamp":" 946957865087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957867639","data":{"timestamp":" 946957867638"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957869262","data":{"timestamp":" 946957869261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957871792","data":{"timestamp":" 946957871792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957873390","data":{"timestamp":" 946957873389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957876612","data":{"timestamp":" 946957876612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957878210","data":{"timestamp":" 946957878210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957880972","data":{"timestamp":" 946957880972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957882579","data":{"timestamp":" 946957882578"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957885043","data":{"timestamp":" 946957885042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957886651","data":{"timestamp":" 946957886650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957888964","data":{"timestamp":" 946957888963"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957890566","data":{"timestamp":" 946957890565"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957892942","data":{"timestamp":" 946957892941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957894545","data":{"timestamp":" 946957894544"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957896820","data":{"timestamp":" 946957896819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957898423","data":{"timestamp":" 946957898422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957900916","data":{"timestamp":" 946957900916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957902484","data":{"timestamp":" 946957902484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957904805","data":{"timestamp":" 946957904804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957906361","data":{"timestamp":" 946957906361"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957908875","data":{"timestamp":" 946957908874"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957910897","data":{"timestamp":" 946957910896"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957911013","data":{"timestamp":" 946957911013"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 9e53ed47-4ddd-481e-acb4-70631da2e65c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957936091","data":{"timestamp":" 946957936091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957937145","data":{"timestamp":" 946957937145"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957944750","data":{"timestamp":" 946957944749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" START_B"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957946188","data":{"timestamp":" 946957946187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957947268","data":{"timestamp":" 946957947267"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957950613","data":{"timestamp":" 946957950612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957951673","data":{"timestamp":" 946957951672"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957954961","data":{"timestamp":" 946957954958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957956027","data":{"timestamp":" 946957956026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957959421","data":{"timestamp":" 946957959421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957960499","data":{"timestamp":" 946957960498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957964223","data":{"timestamp":" 946957964222"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957965275","data":{"timestamp":" 946957965274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957968803","data":{"timestamp":" 946957968802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957969861","data":{"timestamp":" 946957969860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957975593","data":{"timestamp":" 946957975592"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957976636","data":{"timestamp":" 946957976635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957979557","data":{"timestamp":" 946957979557"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957980618","data":{"timestamp":" 946957980617"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957983951","data":{"timestamp":" 946957983950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957985018","data":{"timestamp":" 946957985017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957990863","data":{"timestamp":" 946957990862"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957991944","data":{"timestamp":" 946957991943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957994780","data":{"timestamp":" 946957994779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957995857","data":{"timestamp":" 946957995856"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957999186","data":{"timestamp":" 946957999185"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958000237","data":{"timestamp":" 946958000236"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958003527","data":{"timestamp":" 946958003527"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958004596","data":{"timestamp":" 946958004596"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958007899","data":{"timestamp":" 946958007898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958008961","data":{"timestamp":" 946958008961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958012921","data":{"timestamp":" 946958012920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958013998","data":{"timestamp":" 946958013998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958016825","data":{"timestamp":" 946958016825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958017891","data":{"timestamp":" 946958017891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958022090","data":{"timestamp":" 946958022089"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958023147","data":{"timestamp":" 946958023146"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958028489","data":{"timestamp":" 946958028489"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958029559","data":{"timestamp":" 946958029559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958036394","data":{"timestamp":" 946958036394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958037448","data":{"timestamp":" 946958037448"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958040056","data":{"timestamp":" 946958040055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958041118","data":{"timestamp":" 946958041117"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958043903","data":{"timestamp":" 946958043903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958044957","data":{"timestamp":" 946958044956"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958047856","data":{"timestamp":" 946958047855"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958048926","data":{"timestamp":" 946958048925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958052322","data":{"timestamp":" 946958052321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958052472","data":{"timestamp":" 946958052472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 17e1e65b-6325-4b51-9011-e4f0bd71949f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958074622","data":{"timestamp":" 946958074622"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958082438","data":{"timestamp":" 946958082437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958086974","data":{"timestamp":" 946958086974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958093152","data":{"timestamp":" 946958093152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958097551","data":{"timestamp":" 946958097550"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958103281","data":{"timestamp":" 946958103281"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958107559","data":{"timestamp":" 946958107559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958115835","data":{"timestamp":" 946958115835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958119595","data":{"timestamp":" 946958119595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958124122","data":{"timestamp":" 946958124122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958127779","data":{"timestamp":" 946958127779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958132518","data":{"timestamp":" 946958132518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958136593","data":{"timestamp":" 946958136593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958141341","data":{"timestamp":" 946958141341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958144625","data":{"timestamp":" 946958144625"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958148341","data":{"timestamp":" 946958148341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958152245","data":{"timestamp":" 946958152245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958156748","data":{"timestamp":" 946958156747"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958161392","data":{"timestamp":" 946958161392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958165817","data":{"timestamp":" 946958165817"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958169252","data":{"timestamp":" 946958169252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958173592","data":{"timestamp":" 946958173592"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958179192","data":{"timestamp":" 946958179192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958184229","data":{"timestamp":" 946958184229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958187878","data":{"timestamp":" 946958187878"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958193677","data":{"timestamp":" 946958193672"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 7aed9fa8-bd79-4806-8e5e-86c549aea76b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958223095","data":{"timestamp":" 946958223095"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958225249","data":{"timestamp":" 946958225249"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958227381","data":{"timestamp":" 946958227381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958230605","data":{"timestamp":" 946958230605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958232876","data":{"timestamp":" 946958232876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958235130","data":{"timestamp":" 946958235129"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958238027","data":{"timestamp":" 946958238026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958240215","data":{"timestamp":" 946958240214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958242449","data":{"timestamp":" 946958242448"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958245756","data":{"timestamp":" 946958245756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958247871","data":{"timestamp":" 946958247870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958250004","data":{"timestamp":" 946958250003"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958252978","data":{"timestamp":" 946958252977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958255229","data":{"timestamp":" 946958255228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958257442","data":{"timestamp":" 946958257441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958260466","data":{"timestamp":" 946958260465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958262839","data":{"timestamp":" 946958262838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958265220","data":{"timestamp":" 946958265219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958268301","data":{"timestamp":" 946958268300"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958270427","data":{"timestamp":" 946958270427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958272585","data":{"timestamp":" 946958272584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958275728","data":{"timestamp":" 946958275727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958277956","data":{"timestamp":" 946958277956"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958280116","data":{"timestamp":" 946958280116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958283224","data":{"timestamp":" 946958283223"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958285624","data":{"timestamp":" 946958285623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958288044","data":{"timestamp":" 946958288043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958291200","data":{"timestamp":" 946958291199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958293466","data":{"timestamp":" 946958293466"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958295763","data":{"timestamp":" 946958295763"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958298771","data":{"timestamp":" 946958298771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958301017","data":{"timestamp":" 946958301016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958303205","data":{"timestamp":" 946958303204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958306196","data":{"timestamp":" 946958306193"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958308534","data":{"timestamp":" 946958308534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958310898","data":{"timestamp":" 946958310897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958314052","data":{"timestamp":" 946958314052"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958316418","data":{"timestamp":" 946958316417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958318809","data":{"timestamp":" 946958318808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958321823","data":{"timestamp":" 946958321822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958324136","data":{"timestamp":" 946958324135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958326452","data":{"timestamp":" 946958326451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958329726","data":{"timestamp":" 946958329725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958332013","data":{"timestamp":" 946958332012"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958334292","data":{"timestamp":" 946958334291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958337685","data":{"timestamp":" 946958337684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958340184","data":{"timestamp":" 946958340183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958342615","data":{"timestamp":" 946958342614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958345518","data":{"timestamp":" 946958345518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958347740","data":{"timestamp":" 946958347740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958349965","data":{"timestamp":" 946958349964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958353436","data":{"timestamp":" 946958353435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958355793","data":{"timestamp":" 946958355792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958358115","data":{"timestamp":" 946958358114"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958361216","data":{"timestamp":" 946958361216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958363495","data":{"timestamp":" 946958363494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958365778","data":{"timestamp":" 946958365777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958368836","data":{"timestamp":" 946958368835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958371005","data":{"timestamp":" 946958371004"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958373184","data":{"timestamp":" 946958373184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958376358","data":{"timestamp":" 946958376357"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958378663","data":{"timestamp":" 946958378662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958380928","data":{"timestamp":" 946958380927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958384196","data":{"timestamp":" 946958384195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958386424","data":{"timestamp":" 946958386423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958388668","data":{"timestamp":" 946958388668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958391911","data":{"timestamp":" 946958391910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958394219","data":{"timestamp":" 946958394218"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958396567","data":{"timestamp":" 946958396567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958399744","data":{"timestamp":" 946958399743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958402114","data":{"timestamp":" 946958402113"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958404463","data":{"timestamp":" 946958404463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958407894","data":{"timestamp":" 946958407893"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958408024","data":{"timestamp":" 946958408024"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958426898","data":{"timestamp":" 946958426898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958446299","data":{"timestamp":" 946958446298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" 3e19d8ae-f03a-423f-901d-9111322c8e1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958500842","data":{"timestamp":" 946958500842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_064704"," gameId":" f352b609-672f-4782-99cb-df7dba8e4cc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}